1. get spot list
2. calculate spots weights (max sum of neighbors with one color tiles and weight color), get neighbor list for each spot
3. spot with max weight change color to weight color
4. change maxweightspot color to maxweightspot weight color, sum up this spot with its neighbors, their weights and neighbors, recalculate (sum up) sum weight as one spot
5. log as tiles list with new color
6. sum spot from #4 change color to its weight color, repeat all actions from #4 for this new spot
7. repeat logging for #6 changed tiles
.. (until neighbours.count == 0)


spot merging:
1. 